LUIS FELIPE ROCHINSKI RODRIGUES

Specialist IT Infrastructure & Electrical Engineering Student +55 42 99156 3583 | <u>luisfeliperochinskirodrigues@gmail.com</u> | <u>LinkedIn</u> 24 years old

Address: Ponta Grossa - PR - BRAZIL

I aim to meet the objectives that the company requests, I have advanced experience in IT; Telecom; Electronics; Telephone service and support; Development in graphic programs; AutoCAD; Project Documentation; Web development and management of bank automation using MongoDB and JavaScript.

Skills & Expertise

- Computational automation using node.js and ADB.
- Technical support for users of digital platforms, management of network infrastructure and computers IT sector, maintenance and management of WS 2019.
- Enterprise IT and maintenance of advanced electronic peripherals.
- Development and documentation of ERP system and confidential files.
- Responsible for the IT sector, provided technical support of term transfer printers to customers, experience with Corel Draw, and system development for production, management of E-commerce and other derivatives.
- Inventory control, telephone service, internet support, internet technical assistant, development of WEB systems, configuration of routers and formatting and maintenance of computers, bank services and administrative derivatives.

Professional Experience

• Self Employed

From: 15/10/2021 to date.

Responsibilities: IT infrastructure management; Computational projects of

automation of virtual machines in digital tasks; Web Developer.

• Company: Luxe – Móveis e Decorações

From: 18/10/2020 to 10/10/2021

Position: IT Specialist.

• Company: Klop Informática

From: 23/08/2019 to 30/04/2020

Position/Responsibilities: IT Intern / IT support and service for client enterprises, electronic power peripherals maintenance (Motherboards and nobreaks).

• Company: Baston Industria de Aerossóis

From: 05/07/2016 to 09/09/2016

Position/Responsibilities: Freelancer / Documentation and development of

system and confidential files.

• Company: Usual Etiquetas

From: 27/08/2015 to 10/05/2016

Position: IT Assistent

Company: D`Bug Informática
From: 01/02/2015 to 13/08/2015
Position: Administrative Assistent

Company: D`Bug Informática
From: 01/05/2013 to 02/08/2014
Position: Administrative Intern

Education

• Bachelor's Degree, Electrical Engineering Student UNOPAR – UTFPR | Ponta Grossa, PR

Academic Experience

• Technological innovation project: UTFPR – PG / IUT – PG

From: 13/04/2017 to 23/07/2020.

Research: Creation and development of electronic project.

Intellectual Property: [2] Henrique Terzi Lucchetta / [1] Luis Felipe Rochinski

Rodrigues.

• Extension Project: UTFORCE E-RACING - UTFPR – PG

From: 07/08/2018 to 07/08/2020.

Research: Design engineering / development of 3D encapsulation for telemetry

sensors, and sensor development for electric vehicle suspension.

Supervisor: Professor Frederik Conrad Jensen.

Professional Improvement courses & Certifications

Windows, Word, Excel, PowerPoint and Internet, Publisher / 80hrs

Assembly and Maintenance of Computers / 50hrs

Dreamweaver / Fireworks and Flash / 48hrs

Adobe Photoshop and Corel Draw / 48hrs

F-SAE Vehicle Telemetry Maintenance / 180hrs

Methodology and Analysis and Problem Solving / 16hrs

Business Plan and Feasibility Analysis / 10hrs

Entrepreneurial Profile / 115hrs

Leadership and People Management / 50hrs

Business Strategy / 4hrs

Entrepreneurship / 4hrs

Business Model and Canvas / 9hrs

3D printer / 4hrs

Design Thinking / 8hrs

Microsoft Windows Server 2019 / 15hrs

Web Development / 115hrs